NUNO ARRUDA

Front-End Angular Developer

+1 (757) 529-0315 | nuno@nunoarruda.com | Ponta Delgada, Portugal linkedin.com/in/nunoarruda | github.com/nunoarruda

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Result-Oriented Front-End Angular Engineer with a strong technical skillset, attention to detail, and 18 years of experience. I have a passion for translating beautiful designs into functional user interfaces and building great web applications. I actively learn new technologies and stay up to date on industry trends and advancements. Continued education has allowed me to stay ahead of the curve and deliver exceptional work to each employer I've worked for. I'm currently looking for remote part-time opportunities.

SKILLS

Core: HTML, CSS, Sass, DOM, JavaScript, TypeScript, JSON, AJAX, HTTP, Web APIs, RESTful APIs **Frameworks/Libraries:** Bootstrap, Angular, RxJS, NgRx, Ionic, Angular Material, Wijmo **Other:** Karma, Jasmine, Protractor, Angular Universal, webpack, Node.js, npm, Git/GitHub

EXPERIENCE

Front-End Angular Developer, WR digital GmbH, Remote

Jun 2019 - Sep 2019

- Helped develop <u>Footstock</u>, a gaming web app mixing fantasy football and sports betting.
- Implemented layouts, developed new features, fixed bugs, and wrote documentation.
- Skills Used: Ionic 4, Angular 8, JavaScript, TypeScript, RxJS

Front End Angular Engineer, Rocketloop GmbH, Remote

Dec 2018 - Apr 2019

- Worked on multiple projects in an agile/sprint cycle for this "CTO as a Service" company.
- Implemented layouts, developed new features, fixed bugs, and wrote unit tests.
- Skills Used: Angular 4/5/6/7, TypeScript, RxJS, NgRx, Angular Material, Bootstrap

Senior Frontend Web Developer, Freelancer, Remote

Oct 2013 - Nov 2018

- Provided high-quality frontend web development services for clients worldwide.
- Worked on several projects like emily EMR, Webflow, Adobe Spectrum CSS, or We3 app.
- Skills Used: HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, jQuery, TypeScript, Angular 2/4/5, Ionic 2/3

Web Developer, Anfíbios Lda, Ponta Delgada (Portugal)

Jan 2006 - Sep 2013

- Developed the front-end of customers' websites, newsletters, and web portals.
- Converted designs into HTML/CSS, implemented features, and updated content.
- Skills Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

EDUCATION

Associate degree , Computer Science , University of the People	Jun 2020 (expected)
Front-End Web Developer Nanodegree, Udacity	Apr 2015
CS50x: Introduction to Computer Science I, edX/HarvardX	Apr 2013
IT technician/management course, EPRG	Jul 2005
Web design crash course. VirtualAzores	Jul 2002

LANGUAGES

Portuguese (native) English (advanced)